Charles F. Johnson Jr. Papers
Charles F. Johnson Jr. Papers
- Subject File
  - Employment of Handicapped, 1949; 1953,; 1954 (Box 43)
  - Endicott, N. Y., 1947; 1952,; 1953 (Box 43)
  - Endicott, N. Y. 50th Anniversary Celebration, 1956 (Box 43)
  - Expenses, Personal, 1937; 1947 (Box 43)
  - Flood Control, 1945 (Box 43)
  - Fluoridation, 1953-1955 (Box 43)
  - Food Service, 1955 (Box 43)
  - Fresh Air Fund, 1952; 1953,; 1955 (Box 43)
  - Functional Shoes
    - Reports, 1947; 1954 (Box 44)
    - Users' Comments, 1943 (Box 44)
  - General Electric, 1946-1949 (Box 44)
  - Godman Shoe Co., 1955 (Box 44)
  - Guide Step Shoes, 1953-1955; 1957,; 1958 (Box 44)
  - Harpur College, 1952-1957 (Box 44)
  - Housing, 1949; 1953 (Box 45)
  - Ideal Hospital, undated (Box 45)
  - Inductees Breakfasts, 1950-1953; 2 folders (Box 45)
  - International Business Machines, 1943; 1954 (Box 45)
  - International Shoe Machine Corp., undated (Box 45)
  - Johnson City, 1929; 1938,; 1948,; 1949 (Box 45)
  - Johnson City 60th Anniversary Celebration
    - Correspondence, 1952 (Box 45)
    - Lists, 1952 (Box 46)
    - Programs, Planning, Financial, 1952; 1951,; 1955 (Box 46)
  - Keystone State Shoe Co.
    - Archbald, Pennsylvania, 1946 (Box 46)
    - Financial Reports, 1952; 1953 (Box 46)
    - Forest City, Pennsylvania, 1946; 1948 (Box 46)
    - Mildred, Pennsylvania, 1946-1948 (Box 46)
    - Tunkhannock, Pennsylvania, 1945 (Box 46)
  - Kinney Co. (G. R.), 1953; 1954 (Box 46)
  - Labor Day Celebrations, 1950; 1953,; 1955 (Box 47)
  - Labor Unions, 1938; 1947,; 1948 (Box 47)
  - Legal Documents, 1941; 1943,; 1945,; 1949,; 1951,; 1955 (Box 47)
  - Lehigh Safety Shoe Co., 1930-1932 (Box 47)
  - Letterheads, undated (Box 47)
  - Liberty Shoe Co., 1952 (Box 47)
  - Lists, 1948; 1950-1954,; 1956,; 1959,; undated (Box 47)
  - Marine Corps Citation, 1950 (Box 47)
  - Marine Midland Trust Co. of Southern, N. Y., 1950; 1953,; 1954 (Box 47)
  - Medical Benefits, 1944; 1948,; 1951,; 1953,; 1954,; 1956 (Box 48)
  - Meetings and Minutes, 1949-1952; 1954 (Box 48)
  - Mohawk Airlines, 1952-1955 (Box 48)
  - Montgomery Ward, 1952 (Box 48)
  - Mt. Ettrick Airport, 1947 (Box 48)
  - National Hide Association Award, 1954; 1955 (Box 48)
  - National Labor Relation's Board Investigation, 1938 (Box 48)
  - National Shoe Manufacturers Association, 1949-1951; 1953-1955 (Box 49)
  - Notes on Individual Workers, 1948-1950; 1954-1955,; undated (Box 49)
  - Notes From Secretary, 1946; 1954,; 1955,; undated (Box 49)
  - Orthopedic Shoes, 1954 (Box 49)
  - Pensions
    - Correspondence, Meetings, Reports, 1951-1952 (Box 49)
    - General, 1948; 1949,; 1951,; 1954,; 1955 (Box 49)
  - Personnel Policy and Benefits, 1947-1949; 1951 (Box 49)
  - Polyethylene Shoe Counters, 1952-1955 (Box 50)
  - Prices and Price Control, 1951 (Box 50)
  - Programs, 1949-1957; undated; 3 folders (Box 50)
  - Radio Programs, 1928; 1930,; 1954 (Box 50)
  - Reciprocal Trade Agreements, 1937 (Box 50)
  - Reels, Movie
    - E-J Parade, undated (Box 51)
    - Mr. Charlie's Birthday, 1953 (Box 51)
  - Reports
    - Business Machines, 1949 (Box 51)
    - Footwear, 1951 (Box 51)
    - Investments, 1957 (Box 51)
    - Retail Shoe Stores, undated (Box 51)
  - Roperson Memorial Center, 1955 (Box 52)
  - Rubber Footwear, 1955 (Box 52)
  - Rubber Manufacturers' Association, 1955 (Box 52)
  - Rubber Plant Acquisition, 1953 (Box 52)
  - Scrapbook, undated (Box 52)
    See also Correspondence: Of others: Scrapbook of letters and Scrapbooks series
  - Sears Roebuck, 1952 (Box 52)
  - Servicemen, 1950; 1951 (Box 52)
  - South American Trip, 1954 (Box 52)
  - Statistics Employment, Production, Wages, 1935-1937; 1945,; 1948,; 1949,; 1952,; 1955,; 1956 (Box 53)
  - Stop Work, 1955 (Box 53)
  - Susquehanna Valley Home, 1950-1952 (Box 53)
  - Taft-Hartley Amendment, undated (Box 53)
  - Tapes
    - Charles F. Birthday Parade, 1955 (Box 53)
    - Charles F. Speech, 9 Oct 1950 (Box 53)
  - Triple Cities College, 1946; 1948 (Box 53)
    See also Harpur College
  - United Machinery Corp., 1954 (Box 53)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars Award, 1953 (Box 54)
  - Veterans' Policy, 1941-1951; 1953 (Box 54)
  - Wages, 1945; 1949,; 1951-1954,; 1956,; 1957 (Box 54)
  - Walter L. Johnson Co., 1953-1955 (Box 54)
  - Water Pollution, 1955 (Box 54)
  - Wilson Memorial Hospital, 1932; 1955 (Box 54)
  - Wilson Memorial Hospital Tours, 1953 (Box 54)
  - Workers' (E.-J.) Comments, undated (Box 54)
  - Workmen's Compensation, 1951; 1952 (Box 54)
- Manuscripts
  - About Charles F. Johnson
    - 1955, 1956, undated (Box 55)
  - By Charles F. Johnson
    - Notes, 1949; 1955 (Box 55)
    - Report, 1935 (Box 55)
    - Speeches, 1949; 1950,; 1954,; 1956,; undated (Box 55)
    - Statements, 1934; 1951,; 1953,; undated (Box 55)
    - Transcripts of conversations, 1950; 1951,; 1954,; undated (Box 55)
  - About Endicott-Johnson (Box 55)
  - Of Others
    - 1948, 1955, undated (Box 55)
    - Hopkins, Harry L., 1934 (Box 55)
- George F. Johnson Memorial Fund
  - Correspondence
    - A, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
    - B, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
    - C, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
    - D, E, 1950-1951 (Box 56)
    - Endicott Artistic Memorial Co., 1951 (Box 56)
    - F, G, 1949-1951 (Box 56)
    - H, I, 1948; 1950-1952 (Box 56)
    - J, K, L, 1949-1951 (Box 56)
    - Keck, Charles and Anne, 1950-1951; undated (Box 56)
    - M, 1949-1951 (Box 56)
    - N, O, P, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
    - Q, R, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
    - S, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
    - Sweet, Lillian Johnson, 1949-1951 (Box 57)
      See also Correspondence: Sweet, Lillian Johnson
    - T, U, V, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
    - W, 1949-1951 (Box 57)
    - X, Y, Z, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
  - Arrangements and Meetings (Box 57)
  - Financial and Legal, 1950-1951 (Box 57)
  - Form Letters and Invitations, 1948; 1950,; 1951 (Box 57)
  - Lists
    - Contributions, 1950; 1951 (Box 58)
    - General, 1951 (Box 58)
  - Photos and Sketches, 1951 (Box 58)
  - Programs, 1951 (Box 58)
  - Reception, Oct. 14, 1951 (Box 58)
  - Published Material, 1950; news clippings (Box 58)
- Photographs
  - Chair (Box 59)
  - Endicott-Johnson Chorus
    - Rhoads General Hospital, 1944 (Box 59)
    - Sampson Naval Base, undated (Box 59)
  - Endicott-Johnson Plant, undated (Box 59)
  - Famous People, autographed, undated (Box 59)
  - Houses, undated (Box 59)
  - 1st Infantry Band Performance, 1945 (Box 59)
  - I. B. M. Party, undated (Box 59)
  - Recreation Center, undated (Box 59)
  - Self, undated (Box 59)
  - Self and Family (Box 59)
  - Self with Others, 1899; 1937,; 1948,; 1949,; undated (Box 59)
  - Servicemen, undated (Box 59)
  - Thomas Watson and the Johnsons, undated (Box 59)
  - Wilson Hospital, undated (Box 59)
  - Workers, undated (Box 59)
  - Not Identified, undated (Box 59)
    See also Photograph albums
- Photograph Albums
  - General
    - December 2, 1947 - February 9, 1948 (Box 60)
    - December 29, 1949 - June 26, 1948 (Box 60)
    - July 14, 1948 - November 1, 1948 (Box 60)
    - November 22, 1948 - January 19, 1949 (Box 60)
    - January 20, 1949 - October 29, 1949 (Box 60)
    - August 27, 1949 (Box 60)
    - Labor Day, 1949 (Box 60)
    - September 27, 1949 (Box 60)
    - October 21, 1949 - December, 1949 (Box 60)
    - December, 1949 - January 10, 1950 (Box 60)
    - November 10, 1950 - March 9, 1950 (Box 60)
    - March 9, 1950 - June 1, 1950 (Box 61)
    - June 1, 1950 - August 9, 1950 (Box 61)
    - July 27, 1950 - November 29, 1950 (Box 61)
    - August 7, 1950 - September 27, 1950 (Box 61)
    - Labor Day, 1950 (Box 61)
    - November 29, 1950 - December 14, 1950 (Box 61)
    - United Fund Group, 1950; 2 albums (Box 61)
    - February 3, 1951 - March 28, 1951 (Box 61)
    - March 29, 1951 - May 19, 1951 (Box 61)
    - May 19, 1951 - June 24, 1951 (Box 61)
    - June 27, 1951 - October 13, 1951 (Box 61)
    - October 13, 1951 - December 1, 1951 (Box 61)
    - December 15, 1950 - February 3, 1951 (Box 61)
    - December 3, 1951 - January 3, 1952 (Box 62)
    - January 3, 1952 - January 31, 1952 (Box 62)
    - February 2, 1952 - March 22, 1952 (Box 62)
    - March 29, 1952 - May 8, 1952 (Box 62)
    - May 8, 1952 - September 18, 1952 (Box 62)
    - September 20, 1952 - October 25, 1952 (Box 62)
    - October 25, 1952 - January 10, 1953 (Box 62)
    - January 15, 1953 - February 14, 1953 (Box 62)
    - March 12, 1953 - May 9, 1953 (Box 62)
    - May 9, 1953 - September 17, 1953 (Box 62)
    - Labor Day, 1953 (Box 62)
    - September 19, 1953- October 28, 1953 (Box 62)
    - October 30, 1953 (Box 62)
    - October 28, 1953 - January 11, 1954 (Box 63)
    - January 16, 1954 - March 6, 1954 (Box 63)
    - March 6, 1954 - May 15, 1954 (Box 63)
    - May 22, 1954 - October 9, 1954 (Box 63)
    - Labor Day, 1954; 2 albums (Box 63)
    - October 10, 1954 - January 6, 1955 (Box 63)
    - January 6, 1955 - February 5, 1955 (Box 63)
    - February 5, 1955 - April 1, 1955 (Box 63)
    - April 4, 1955 - May 14, 1955 (Box 63)
    - May 14, 1955 - August 4, 1955 (Box 63)
    - August 4, 1955 - September 24, 1955 (Box 63)
    - Labor Day, 1955 (Box 63)
    - September 24, 1955 - October 20, 1955 (Box 63)
    - October 21, 1955 - January 7, 1956 (Box 63)
    - 1956 United Fund (Box 64)
    - January 7, 1956 - January 28, 1956 (Box 64)
    - January 29, 1956 - February 26, 1956 (Box 64)
    - February 26, 1956 - April 19, 1956 (Box 64)
    - April 19, 1956 - April 23, 1956 (Box 64)
    - April 23, 1956 - May 30, 1956 (Box 64)
    - June 10, 1956 - September 8, 1956 (Box 64)
    - August 25, 1956 Endicott's 50th Anniversary, 2 albums (Box 64)
    - Labor Day, 1956 (Box 64)
    - September 9, 1956 - October 13, 1956 (Box 64)
    - October 13, 1956 - January 9, 1957 (Box 64)
    - January 12, 1956 - March 9, 1957 (Box 64)
    - March 9, 1957 (Box 64)
    - 1957-1958 (Box 64)
  - Inductees
    - December 6, 1950 - January 22, 1951 (Box 65)
    - February 5, 1951 - February 6, 1951 (Box 65)
    - February 6, 1951 - March 6, 1951 (Box 65)
    - March 6, 1951 - March 26, 1951 (Box 65)
    - March 26, 1951 - May 21, 1951 (Box 65)
    - May 26, 1951 - August 1, 1951 (Box 65)
    - August 1, 1951 - December 12, 1951 (Box 65)
    - October 2, 1951 - January 17, 1952 (Box 65)
    - January 17, 1952 - February 18, 1952 (Box 65)
    - February 18, 1952 - March 14, 1952 (Box 65)
    - March 19, 1952 - April 14, 1952 (Box 65)
    - April 14, 1952 - July 24, 1952 (Box 66)
    - July 24, 1952 - September 18, 1952 (Box 66)
    - September 18, 1952 - October 17, 1952 (Box 66)
    - October 17, 1952 - December 10, 1952 (Box 66)
    - December 10, 1952 - January 26, 1953 (Box 66)
    - January 26, 1953 - February 19, 1953 (Box 66)
    - February 19, 1953 - March 19, 1953 (Box 66)
    - March 19, 1953 - April 17, 1953 (Box 66)
    - April 17, 1953 - April 21, 1953 (Box 66)
    - April 21, 1953 - May 20, 1953 (Box 66)
    - April 20, 1953 - June 15, 1953 (Box 66)
    - June 15, 1953 - July 7, 1953 (Box 66)
    - July 7, 1953 - August 11, 1953 (Box 66)
  - Workers' Homes
    - March 27, 1949 - May 8, 1949 (Box 67)
    - June 1, 1949 - October 20, 1949 (Box 67)
    - November 27, 1949 - March 19, 1950 (Box 67)
    - April 16, 1950 - June 25, 1950 (Box 67)
    - May 9, 1950 (Box 67)
- Plaques
  - 1935
    - From Fine Workers (Box 68)
  - 1950
    - Bowling Tournament from E.-J. A. A. Workers (Box 68)
    - In Memory C. Fred Johnson (Box 68)
    - Kiwanis International-Honorary Membership (Box 68)
  - 1952
    - American Dads Award, 2 copies (Box 68)
    - Veterans of Foreign Wars (Box 68)
  - 1957
    - For outstanding service to Johnson City Y.M.C.A. (Box 68)
  - Undated
    - Golden Anniversary from E. J. Workers, N. Y. Division (Box 68)
- Workers' Pages
  - 1948, 10 folders (Box 69)
  - 1949: January-May, 4 folders (Box 69)
  - 1949: June-December, 6 folders (Box 70)
  - 1950: January-June, 6 folders (Box 70)
  - 1950: July-December, 6 folders (Box 71)
  - 1951: January-May, 5 folders (Box 71)
  - 1951: June-December, 7 folders (Box 72)
  - 1952: January-March, 3 folders (Box 72)
  - 1952: April-December, 9 folders (Box 73)
  - 1953: January-October, 10 folders (Box 74)
  - 1953: November-December, 2 folders (Box 75)
  - 1954: January-August, 8 folders (Box 75)
  - 1954: September-December, 4 folders (Box 76)
  - 1955: January-June, 6 folders (Box 76)
  - 1955: July-December, 6 folders (Box 77)
  - 1956: January-March, 3 folders (Box 77)
  - 1956: April-December, 9 folders (Box 78)
  - 1959: May-December, 8 folders (Box 79)
- Workers' petitions
  - 1946-1949 (Box 80)
  - 1950-1952, 1956 (Box 81)
- Published Material
  - Advertisements, 1937; 1952-1954,; undated (Box 82)
  - Articles About, 1952; 1954 (Box 82)
  - Articles By, 1955 (Box 82)
  - Articles About Endicott-Johnson, 1934; 1943,; 1949,; 1950,; 1952,; 1955,; 1956 (Box 82)
  - Brochures
    - Endicott-Johnson, 1916; 1919,; 1923-1926,; 1937,; 1948,; 1953-1955,; undated (Box 82)
    - Others, 1927; 1930,; 1948-1951,; 1953,; 1954,; undated (Box 82)
  - Catalogs
    - Fall 1913/Spring 1914 (Box 82)
  - Magazines
    - EJ Workers Magazine, Apr 1925; Sep 1925,; Oct 1925 (Box 82)
  - News Letters "The Labor Market in Tennessee"
    - 1950, 1951, 1953-1956 (Box 82)
    - 1957-1959 (Box 83)
  - Newspaper Clippings
    - About Charles F. Johnson Jr.
      - 1935, 1937, 1940-1941, 1946-1953, 9 folders (Box 83)
      - 1954-1955, includes C. F. J. Jr. Jubilee, 1955; 3 folders (Box 84)
      - 1956-1957, 1959, 3 folders (Box 85)
    - About Others
      - Broome County, 1950 (Box 85)
      - C. Fred John, 1950; 1954 (Box 85)
      - Endicott, N. Y. Golden Year, 1956 (Box 85)
      - Endicott-Johnson Corp, 1934; 1935,; 1937-1944,; 1946-1950,; 1952-1956,; undated; 5 folders (Box 86)
      - Endicott-Johnson Athletic Association, 1947; 1949 (Box 87)
      - George F. Johnson, 1935; 1938,; 1939,; 1948,; 1950,; 1951,; 1953,; 1956; 2 folders (Box 87)
      - Johnson City, 1952 (Box 87)
      - Wilson Hospital, 1950; 1952,; undated (Box 87)
      - World War II, 14 Aug 1945 (Box 87)
    - By Charles F. Johnson Jr., 1937; 1938,; 1942,; 1943,; 1948,; 1956 (Box 87)
  - Notices, 1942 (Box 87)
  - Press Releases, 1931; 1937,; 1949,; 1950,; 1959 (Box 87)
- Scrapbooks
  See also Correspondence: Of others: Scrapbook of letters and Subject files: Scrapbook
  - E.J. Workers Daily News Scrapbooks, set of 44, numbered
    - No. 1, 4/22/47-8/8/47 (Oversize 1)
    - No. 1A, 8/11/47-11/28/47 (Oversize 1)
    - No. 2, [11/28/47]-5/17/48; [cover date: 12/01/47] (Oversize 2)
    - No. 3, 5/22/48-10/30/48; [cover date: 5/20/48-10/28/48] (Oversize 2)
    - No. 4, 11/1/48-2/5/49 (Oversize 3)
    - No. 5, [2/12/49-7/19/49]; [cover date: 2/5/49 to ] (Oversize 3)
    - No. 6, 7/26/49-10/6/49 (Oversize 4)
    - No. 7, 10/13/49-12/9/49 (Oversize 4)
    - No. 8, 12/10/49-2/7/50 (Oversize 5)
    - No. 9, [2/11/50-5/8/50]; [cover date: 2/2/50-5/9/50] (Oversize 5)
    - No. 10, 5/10/50-8/9/50 (Oversize 6)
    - No. 11, 8/26/50-[11/30/50]; [cover date: 11/11/50] (Oversize 6)
    - No. 12, 11/28/50-1/16/51 (Oversize 7)
    - No. 13, [1/22/51]-3/29/51; [cover date: 1/20/50] (Oversize 7)
    - No. 14, 3/29/51-5/22/51 (Oversize 8)
    - No. 15, [5/22/51]-9/11/51; [cover date: 5/23/51] (Oversize 8)
    - No. 16, 9/24/51-11/29/51 (Oversize 9)
    - No. 17, 11/30/51-12/21/51 (Oversize 9)
    - No. 18, [1/2/52-6/25/52]; [cover date: 1/1/52-6/27/52] (Oversize 10)
    - No. 19, [1/8/52-9/29/52]; [cover date: 9/1/52-9/27/52] (Oversize 10)
    - No. 20, [1/11/52]-10/17/52; [cover date: 1/10/52] (Oversize 11)
    - No. 21, [6/27/52]-12/26/52; [cover date: 7/11/52] (Oversize 11)
    - No. 22, [10/4/52]-4/13/53; [cover: 10/3/52; "Parties"] (Oversize 12)
    - No. 23, 10/18/52-5/21/53; [cover: "Induction breakfasts"] (Oversize 12)
    - No. 24, [1/3/53]-9/12/53; [cover date: 1/1/53, second date not shown] (Oversize 13)
    - No. 25, 4/17/53-12/18/53; [second date not on cover] (Oversize 13)
    - No. 26, [5/27/53-8/12/53]; [cover date: 5/26/53, no second date shown] (Oversize 14)
    - No. 27, 9/21/53-8/10/54; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 14)
    - No. 28, [12/21/53]-5/24/54; [cover date: 12/31/53; "Parties"] (Oversize 15)
    - No. 29, 8/18/54-11/16/54; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 15)
    - No. 30, [9/13/54]-3/14/55; [cover date: 9/11/54; "Parties"] (Oversize 16)
    - No. 31, 11/18/54-5/25/55; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 16)
    - No. 32, [3/22/55]-12/12/55; [cover date: 3/21/55; "Parties"] (Oversize 17)
    - No. 33, 5/27/55-8/22/55; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 17)
    - No. 34, 7/27/55-10/21/55 (Oversize 18)
    - No. 35, 10/24/55-12/14/55; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 18)
    - No. 36, 12/16/55-9/21/56; [cover: "Parties"] (Oversize 19)
    - No. 37, 12/21/55-3/23/56; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 19)
    - No. 38, 3/24/56-[6/8/56]; [cover date: 6/4/56; "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 20)
    - No. 39, 6/18/56-[8/23/56]; [cover date: 8/22/55; "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 20)
    - No. 40, 8/22/56-10/22/56; [cover: "Miscellaneous"] (Oversize 21)
    - No. 41, 9/24/56-3/4/57; [cover: "Parties"] (Oversize 21)
    - No. 42, 10/23/56-[2/20/57]; [2nd date not on cover; “Miscellaneous”] (Oversize 22)
    - No. 43, [3/11/57-11/4/57]; [no cover dates given] (Oversize 22)
    - No. 44, [2/23/57-4/17/59]; [no cover dates given] (Oversize 22)
  - New York Politics (Averill Harriman) Scrapbooks
    Consists of 36 scrapbooks of paper clippings (25 Sep 1954-24 Dec 1958) nearly all relating to Averill Harriman and his political rise, life, and events as governor of New York State until his defeat in the 1958 elections, taken from various (and mostly) New York State papers. Also contains clippings on a variety of political and economic issues (tariffs, etc.).
    - No. 1, 25 Sep 1954-3 Nov 1954 (Oversize 23)
    - No. 2, 23 Dec 1954-11 Jan 1955 (Oversize 24)
    - No. 3, 12 Jan 1955-27 Jan 1955 (Oversize 24)
    - No. 4, 27 Jan 1955-28 Feb 1955 (Oversize 25)
    - No. 5, 1 Mar 1955-14 Apr 1955 (Oversize 25)
    - No. 6, 15 Apr 1955-25 May 1955 (Oversize 26)
    - No. 7, 25 May 1955-5 Jul 1955 (Oversize 26)
    - No. 8, 5 Jul 1955-9 Sep 1955 (Oversize 27)
    - No. 9, 9 Sep 1955-1 Dec 1955 (Oversize 27)
    - No. 10, 1 Dec 1955-31 Dec 1955 (Oversize 28)
    - No. 11, 1 Jan 1956-17 Feb 1956 (Oversize 28)
    - No. 12, 18 Feb 1956-23 May 1956 (Oversize 29)
    - No. 13, 25 May 1956-30 Jun 1956 (Oversize 29)
    - No. 14, 1 Jul 1956-7 Aug 1956 (Oversize 30)
    - No. 15, 7 Aug 1956-4 Sep 1956 (Oversize 30)
    - No. 16, 5 Sep 1956-23 Nov 1956 (Oversize 31)
    - No. 17, 23 Nov 1956-31 Dec 1956 (Oversize 31)
    - No. 18, 1 Jan 1957-1 Feb 1957 (Oversize 32)
    - No. 19, 1 Feb 1957-1 Mar 1957 (Oversize 32)
    - No. 20, 1 Mar 1957-26 Mar 1957 (Oversize 33)
    - No. 21, 26 Mar 1957-20 Apr 1957 (Oversize 33)
    - No. 22, 20 Apr1957-31 May 1957 (Oversize 34)
    - No. 23, 1 Jun 1957-26 Jul 1957 (Oversize 34)
    - No. 24, 27 Jul 1957-24 Sep 1957 (Oversize 35)
    - No. 25, 24 Sep 1957-7 Nov 1957 (Oversize 35)
    - No. 26, 7 Nov 1957-10 Dec 1957 (Oversize 36)
    - No. 27, 11 Dec 1957-9 Jan 1958 (Oversize 36)
    - No. 28, 9 Jan 1958-9 Feb 1958 (Oversize 37)
    - No. 29, 9 Feb 1958-19 Mar 1958 (Oversize 37)
    - No. 30, 15 Mar 1958-26 Apr 1958 (Oversize 38)
    - No. 31, 26 Apr 1958-19 Jun 1958 (Oversize 38)
    - [No. 32], 19 Jun 1958-22 Aug 1958; cover labeled "No. 26" (Oversize 39)
    - [No. 33], 22 Aug 1958-19 Sep 1958; cover labeled "No. 28" (Oversize 39)
    - [No. 34], 19 Sep 1958-15 Oct 1958; cover labeled "No. 29" (Oversize 40)
    - No. 35, 16 Oct 1958-3 Nov 1958 (Oversize 40)
    - No. 36, 3 Nov 1958-24 Dec 1958 (Oversize 40)
  - Other Scrapbooks
    - The Endicott-Johnson Proposition, 1927; Sales/advertising material for shoe dealers (Oversize 59)
    - Charles F. Johnson Jr., October 22nd, 1947; 60th Birthday celebration book includes photos, newspaper clippings, telegrams, cards. (Oversize 45)
    - My 61st Birthday, 22 Oct 1948; Includes photos, newspaper clippings, telegrams, cards. (Oversize 46)
    - My 62nd Birthday, 22 Oct 1949; Includes photos, newspaper clippings, telegrams, cards. (Oversize 47)
    - Petition signed by Endicott-Johnson workers upon C.F.J. Jr.’s receipt of D.S.M. from American Legion, 18 May 1950; Workers signatures. (Oversize 56)
    - Chas. F. Johnson Jr. 63rd Birthday, 22 Oct 1950; Includes photos, newspaper clippings, telegrams, cards. (Oversize 48)
    - My Trip to California, 1950; Recipient of the National American Legion Distinguished Service Medal Award. Includes letters, photos, newspaper clippings (Oversize 49)
    - 64 Years Chas. F. Johnson Jr., 22 Oct 1951; 64th Birthday album scrapbook, with photos, clippings, telegrams, and cards. (Oversize 50)
    - 65 Mr. Charlie, 22 Oct 1952; 65th Birthday album scrapbook, with photos, clippings, telegrams, and cards. (Oversize 51)
    - Johnson City 60th Anniversary Celebration., 1952; 5 volumes; photos and clippings
      - Vol. 1 (Oversize 61)
      - Vol. 2 (Oversize 61)
      - Vol. 3 (Oversize 62)
      - Vol. 4 (Oversize 62)
      - [Vol. 5] (Oversize 63)
      - Award plaque (Oversize 63)
    - 66 Mr. Charlie, 22 Oct 1953; 66th Birthday album scrapbook, with photos, clippings, telegrams, and cards. (Oversize 52)
    - For You, Mr. Charlie on your 66th Birthday, West Branch, October 22, 1953; Photo and workers signatures from the E.J. West Branch, October 22, 1953. (Oversize 56)
    - Mr. Charlie, 22 Oct 1954; 67th Birthday album scrapbook, with photos, clippings, telegrams, cards, children’s artwork (Oversize 53)
    - Medal of Merit Award of National Hide Association, 1955; photos, letters, telegrams, newspaper clippings (Oversize 57)
    - Our Pledge to Mr. Charlie, 1955; worker's signatures (Oversize 58)
    - Golden Anniversary of C.F.J.Jr. employment with Endicott-Johnson Corp., 1955; 4 volumes
      - Vol. 1 Letters, telegrams, cards (Oversize 41)
      - Vol. 2 News clippings (Oversize 42)
      - Vol. 3 Photos (Oversize 43)
      - Vol. 4 Photos and news clippings (Oversize 44)
    - Charles F. Johnson, October 22, 1956; 69th Birthday album scrapbook, with photos, clippings, telegrams, cards, and greetings from schoolchildren. (Oversize 54)
    - Hold Fast to That Which is Good, employee signatures (Oversize 55)
    - Get Well Message from 20,000 Workers, undated (Oversize 57)
- Miscellaneous (all oversize)
  - Awards and Photographs, undated (Oversize 64)
  - Binghamton Post 80 of American Legion on Birthday, undated (Oversize 60)
  - Official Nomination as member of council for St. Univ. at Harpur College, 1954 (Oversize 60)
  - Pen and Ink Painting of C. F. J. Jr., undated (Oversize 60)
  - Phonograph Record of Presentation of D.S.M. to C.F.J. Jr. by American Legion, 1950; 33 1/3 rpm (Oversize 60)
  - Tribute to C. F. J. Jr. on his 68th Birthday by Winius Brandon Co., 1955 (Oversize 60)